Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young.
1926-1999
1968-1997
UCLA Library Special Collections
University of California, Los Angeles. Office of the Chancellor
UARC.0594
273.8 Linear Feet (622 boxes, 25 cartons)
Record Series 549 contains the administrative files of UCLA Chancellor Charles E. Young, generated primarily between 1968-1997.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Record Series 594 was received in 2005 and 2008 from the UCLA Chancellor's Communications Services (CCS).
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9944751133606533
Biographical History
Charles E. Young served as UCLA's fourth Chancellor from 1968-1997.
Scope and Content
Record Series 549 contains the administrative files of UCLA Chancellor Charles E. Young. Files regard Instructional Units; Academic and Staff Personnel; Universitywide Administration; Board of Regents; Campus Administration; Public Service; Spch. Campus Administration; Extramural Support; Systemwide Administration; Campus Management; Student Services and Activities; Organized Research and Museums; Intramural Relations; Instructional Support Units; Chancellor's Advisory Committee on the Status of Women; University Policies Commission; Governmental Relations; Public relations; LA Division Academic Senate; Student Associations; Plant Development and Maintenance; Instruction; Museum of Cultural History; Graduate School of Education; Academic Senate; Public Ceremonies; Museums and Special Collections; University of California Campuses; Campus Human Resources; and Extended University.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
- Certificates of congratulations upon C. Young's inauguration as Chancellor., 1969. (Box 1)
- Inauguration ephemera., 1969. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Certificates of congratulations upon C. Young's inauguration as Chancellor., 1969. (Box 2, Folder 2-5)
- Index: V10#1. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #3., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Index: V10HS. Instructional Units-Duplication of High School Courses., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Index: V10HS. Instructional Units-Duplication of High School Courses., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Index: V10#1. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #2., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Index: V10#1. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #1., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Index: V10#2. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #5., 1984. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Index: V10#2. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #4., 1984. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Index: VN46. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences., 1977-1990. (Box 3, Folder 569)
- Index: VN46/ECON. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Economics - (Academic Senate Review)., 1976-1993. (Box 3, Folder 570)
- Index: V10#2. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #3., 1984. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Index: V10#2. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #2., 1984. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Index: V10#2. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-General #1., 1984. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Index: V10HS. Instructional Units-Duplication of High School Courses., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Index: B19/L5. Universitywide Administration-Library Policy Task Force., 1974. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary #1., 1975-1977. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary Committee., 1976-1977. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1990-1991. (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1991-1992. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Index: B19/O2. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on Obligations/Responsibilities of Faculty/Administrators., 1970. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Index: B19/S8. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on Student Participation in University Governance., 1975-1977. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Index: B19/S88. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on Student Regulations., 1970-1971. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Index: BN1. Universitywide Administration-Project Clean Air., 1969-1971. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Index: VN46/AERO. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Aerospace Studies., 1950-1984. (Box 4, Folder 569)
- Index: VN46/ECON-01. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Economics - Economics/Business Major., 1979-1991. (Box 4, Folder 570)
- Index: BP1. Universitywide Administration-University Engineering Program., 1978-1984. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Index: H30. Intramural Relations-Regulations and Procedures-Federal., 1968-1977. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary #3., 1978. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary #2., 1978. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Index: VN46/ARTHRO. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Anthropology., 1948-1993. (Box 5, Folder 569)
- Index: VN46/GEOG. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Geography - Review., 1976-1991. (Box 5, Folder 570)
- Index: VN46/ARTHRO-01. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Anthropology - Human Relations Area Files., 1988-1991. (Box 6, Folder 569)
- Index: VN46/GEOG. Instructional Units - College of Letters & Science - Division of Social Sciences - Geography., 1947-1991. (Box 6, Folder 570)
- Index: DA52/Spec. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Files - Speeches., 1983-1984. (Box 7, Folder unknown container)
- Index: W10. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing Network - Policy on Use., 1965-1977. (Box 7, Folder unknown container)
- Index: V10/Jour. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Journalism #5., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Index: V10/PhSci. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Physical Sciences., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Index: V10/Spch. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Speech #4., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Index: V10/Jour. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Journalism #4., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Index: V10/Jour. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Journalism #3., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Index: V10/Jour. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Journalism #2., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Index: V10/Jour. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Journalism #1., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Index: V10/Lsci. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Life Sciences #3., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Index: V10/Lsci. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Life Sciences #2., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Index: V10/Lsci. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Life Sciences #1., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Index: V10/PE. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Physical Education., 1971. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Index: A67/E3. Board of Regents - Committees-Educational Policy., 1977, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Index: B16/G4. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Advisory Comm. on Institute of Geophysics., 1971-1983. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Index: B16/I6. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Comm. on Instructional Improvement Programs., 1978-1979. (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Index: B16/L4. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Advisory Comm. for Learning Resources., 1978. (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Index: B16/L5. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Advisory Council on Education for Libraries., 1987. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Index: B16/L6. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Library Council., 1973-1992. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Index: B16/M5. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Council of Med. School Deans., 1975. (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Index: B19/E8. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on the Extended University., 1972-1976. (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Index: B19/E8. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on the Extended University-Reports., 1971-1972. (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Index: B19/E8. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on the Extended University-Reports., 1971. (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Index: B19/E8. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on the Extended University-Reports., 1970. (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Index: A67/F5. Board of Regents - Committees-Finance., 1978. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Index: B19/G7. Universitywide Administration-Task Force on the Growth Plan., 1971-1972. (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Index: A67/G7. Board of Regents - Committees-Standing Committees-Grounds and Buildings., 1979, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Index: B16/A25. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-President's Administrative Council., 1976. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Index: B16/A8. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Intercampus Athletic Advisory Comm., 1971-1974. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Index: B16/C5. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Policy Comm. on UC-Chile Coop. Program., 1972-1979. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Index: B16/E5. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Engineering Advisory Council., 1970. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Index: B16/E6. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Council on Engineering Education., 1971-1977. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Index: B16/F4#1. Universitywide Administration-Advisory Boards-Federal Regulations Advisory Council., 1978-1983. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Index: DA80. Campus Administration- Chancellor's Office - Academic Administration., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Index: YD31. Public Service-Urban Crisis Programs-Southern California College., 1971. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Index: YD40. Public Service-Urban Crisis Programs-Urban Centers-General., 1982. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Index: H27. Public Service-Vocational Education., 1969-1976. (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Index: DA80. Campus Administration- Chancellor's Office - Academic Administration., 1987-1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Index: DA81. Campus Administration- Chancellor's Office - Academic Change & Curriculum Development #2., 1973-1974. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Index: DA81. Campus Administration- Chancellor's Office - Academic Change & Curriculum Development #1., 1970-1973. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Index: V10/TT. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Teacher Training #3., 1971. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Index: V10/TT. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Teacher Training #2., 1971. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Index: V10/TT. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review-Teacher Training #1., 1971. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Index: YD22. Public Service-Urban Crisis Programs-Pico Union Project., 1970. (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Index: DA75. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Executive Vice Chancellor., 1975-1987. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1981-1984. (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Index: DA90.5. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Associate Vice Chancellor - Research Programs., 1984-1989. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Index: H27. Intramural Relations - Anti-Riot Legislation and Regulations, General., 1971. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Index: Y04. Public Service - California Regional Medical Programs., 1971-1977. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Index: DA75 - WPG. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Executive Vice Chancellor - William P. Gerberding., 1975-1976. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Index: DA75 - DSS. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Executive Vice Chancellor - David S. Saxon., 1972-1975. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1991. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1990-1991. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1989-1990. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1989. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Index: DA90 - Spch. Campus Administration - Chancellor's Office - Research - Speeches of Albert A. Barber., 1985-1989. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Index: SEALED. SEALED. (Box 11, Folder unknown container)
- Index: B19. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-General., 1979-1989. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Index: B19-A. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-Academic Salary & Task Force on AIDS., 1976-1986. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Index: B19-B. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-Task Force on Black Student Eligibility., 1989. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Index: B19-B. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-Task Force on Black Student Eligibility., 1988. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Index: B19-B. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-Task Force on Black Student Eligibility., 1987. (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Index: B19-B. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-Budget Systems Task Force., 1973. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Index: B19-C. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-CA Community College Task Force., 1986. (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Index: B19-C. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-CA Community College Task Force., 1985. (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Index: B19-C. Systemwide Administration-President's Task Forces-Capitol Charges, Clinical Teaching & Contracting., 1986-1988. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies., 1981. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies., 1977-1978. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies., 1975-1976. (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies., 1974-1975. (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies-Progress Report #2., 1971-1973. (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies-Progress Report #1., 1971-1973. (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies., 1971-1972. (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Index: K49/FORD. Extramural Support-Ford Foundation-Ethnic Studies-Correspondence., 1970-1977. (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Index: DA78. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Institutional Relations-Vice Chancellor., 1991-1992. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Index: DA78. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Institutional Relations-Vice Chancellor., 1989-1990. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Index: DA78. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Institutional Relations-Vice Chancellor., 1987-1988. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Index: DA78. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Institutional Relations-Vice Chancellor., 1985-1986. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Index: DA78. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Institutional Relations-Vice Chancellor., 1980-1984. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Index: DA78. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Institutional Relations-Vice Chancellor., 1969-1979. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor., 1989. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor., 1987. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1989-1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1980-1981. (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1979-1980. (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1978-1979. (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1977-1978. (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1976-1977. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1975-1976. (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1974-1975. (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1973-1974. (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1972-1973. (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1988-1989. (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1987-1988. (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1986-1987. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1985-1986. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1984-1985. (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1983-1984. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1982-1983. (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary Payment and Funding-Academic Salary., 1981-1982. (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor., 1983-1985. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor-Budget., 1981. (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor-Budget-1979- 80., 1980. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor-Budget., 1976-1977. (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Index: DA87. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Office-Administrative Vice Chancellor-1976-77 budget request., 1975. (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Index: DE19/T3L5. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Planning Office-Budget-Libraries., 1974. (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Index: DE19/T307. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Planning Office-Budget-Organized Research., 1973-1974. (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Index: DE43. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Planning Office-Cooperation with other Planning Groups., 1976-1981. (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Index: DE43/C1. Campus Administration-Chancellor's Planning Office-Cooperation with other Planning Groups- Campus Planning/Research., 1976. (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Index: BD31/C6. Systemwide Administration-Business and Finance-Computer Policy Board., 1980. (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Index: BD31/C6. Systemwide Administration-Business and Finance-Computer Policy Board., 1978. (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Index: BD31/C6. Systemwide Administration-Business and Finance-Computer Policy Board., 1975-1976. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Index: V10/Spch. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review Speech., 1941-1971. (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Index: V10/Spch. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review Speech., Undated. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Index: V10/Spch. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review Speech #2., 1971. (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Index: V10/Spch. Instructional Units-Programmatic Review Speech #1., 1971. (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments., 1985-1987. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments., 1983-1984. (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments., 1982. (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments-Faculty Displacement., 1982. (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments., 1975-1981. (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments., 1973-1974. (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Index: NA16. Academic Personnel-Personnel Actions-Tenure Appointments., 1970-1972. (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Index: NB16/S8. Academic Personnel-Salary and Payment Funding-Summer Employment., 1975-1986. (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary and Payment Funding-Academic Salary Scales., 1981. (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary and Payment Funding-Academic Salary Scales., 1979-1985. (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary and Payment Funding-Academic Salary Scales., 1979-1980. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Index: NB18. Academic Personnel-Salary and Payment Funding-Academic Salary Scales-Academic Compensation Committee., 1979. (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles Olympic Organizing Committee files., 1974-1984. (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes files regarding use of administrative office building and Drake Stadium; insurance; and previous Olympic Games.
- Index: B16. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-General., 1985. (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Index: B16-A. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1983-1989. (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Index: B16-A. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1979-1982. (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Index: B16-B. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1980-1984. (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Index: B16-C. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1988. (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Index: B16-C. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1982-1988. (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Index: B16-D. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1974-1986. (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Index: B16-E. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1981-1987. (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Index: B16-F. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1977-1988. (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Index: B16-H. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-Health, Safety & Environment Advisory Comm., 1988. (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Index: B16-S. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1972-1988. (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Index: B16-T. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1979-1987. (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Index: B16-U. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1978-1988. (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Index: B16-I. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1981. (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Index: B16-J. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-Joint Graduate Board., 1984. (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Index: B16-L. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-UC Committee on Learning Disabilities., 1987. (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Index: B16-M. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-Exec. Comm. of Institute of Marine Resources., 1987. (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Index: B16-M. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-UC Mosquito Control Research Program., 1985. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Index: B16-M. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-UC Mosquito Control Research Program., 1982. (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Index: B16-P. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards-Pacific Rim Executive Committee., 1985. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Index: B16-R. Systemwide Administration-President's Advisory Boards., 1982-1988. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Index: BB43. Systemwide Administration-Policy Manuals-Academic Personnel Manual., 1982-1983. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Index: BB43. Systemwide Administration-Policy Manuals-Academic Personnel Manual., 1973-1976. (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Index: BB52. Systemwide Administration-Policy Manuals-University Regulations., 1960-1981. (Box 22, Folder 3)